Fernando Nascimento Oliveira

Programador

Programmer from Rio and Developer 4 years ago, creative, self-taught, able to learn and quickly adapt to new tools and technologies. I always enjoyed technology and software development. I started to program at fourteen years old and looking for improvement further and further.

Work History

2021-12 Full-stack Developer (Intern Program)

- present Link Informática, Rio de janeiro

I developed mobile apps, web systems for clients and a SAS platform for intern purposes. everything was made with react and

react-native.

- 2020-07 Império das pizzas, Rio de janeiro

IT assistant

I worked at computer and Network assembly and maintenance, besides that, I build a storefront and back-office system.

Education

2019-04

2021-02 Ciência da computação, Superior

- 2021-07 Unicarioca, Rio de Janeiro

2018-02 **Técnico em Informática, Ensino Médio**

- 2020-11 Lemos de Castro, Rio de janeiro

% Projects

2021-12 **Programmer**

- present PDV Link

A react-native-cli is a POS (point of sale) app with sqlite database

in order to work offline.

2020-01 Manager and programmer

EasyWork is a SaaS of jobs (made with PHP), which connects a worker and in need person. The project did develop as my final

paper in high school.

2019-02 **Programmer**

- 2020-04 Império das pizzas

I developed with PHP an ordering platform with complete financial

and product management.

A Personal Info

Email

fernandinho.nco@gmail.com

Phone

(21) 99789-5329

GitHub

https://github.com/NOX-0202

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fernando-

oliveira/

Website

https://nox-0202.github.io/

Address

Praça seca, Rio de Janeiro

Languages

Inglês (Avançado)

Skills

Pacote Office

Windows e linux

Html/css

LibreOffice

JavaScript

Jquery

React

React Native

Nodejs

PHP

laravel

MySQL

MongoDB



<u>P</u>	Courses
-	Courses

Python (Básico)

Full Stack PHP Developer

Complete PHP online course given by uplnside.

Ruby

Ruby

Ruby

Ruby

Ruby

Python (Básico)

Postgress

2020-05 Aprenda PHP do Zero Com Facilidade e Faça Sites Dinâmicos, Online WEB programing with PHP 2020-07 HTML5 e CSS3 essentials Complete WEB online course given by upInside. 2020-01 The Complete JavaScript Course 2021: From Zero to Expert! Curso completo de Javascript 2018-02 Curso em vídeo de python Free online course produced by Curso em video 2019-08 Curso de Montagem e manutenção de computadores

On lemos de castro school

© Certificates

2020-07	HTML5 e CSS3 essentials
2020-05	Aprenda PHP do Zero Com Facilidade e Faça Sites Dinâmicos, Online
2018-02	Curso em vídeo - Python
2020-08	Dev Tools essentials
2019-06	Curso de Montagem e manutenção de computadores